export const words = [
  {
    answer: "dog",
    question: "A friendly and loyal domesticated animal often kept as a pet.",
  },
  {
    answer: "cat",
    question:
      "A furry animal that can be a loving companion and is known for chasing mice.",
  },
  {
    answer: "book",
    question:
      "A collection of pages with stories or information that you can read.",
  },
  {
    answer: "rainbow",
    question: "A colorful arch in the sky that appears after it rains.",
  },
  {
    answer: "flower",
    question:
      "A beautiful plant that grows in gardens, often with colorful petals.",
  },
  {
    answer: "bicycle",
    question: "A two-wheeled vehicle that you can ride by pedaling.",
  },
  {
    answer: "friend",
    question: "Someone you like and enjoy spending time with.",
  },
  {
    answer: "cake",
    question: "A delicious dessert often served on birthdays with sweet icing.",
  },
  {
    answer: "sun",
    question:
      "The bright, warm ball of light in the sky that gives us daylight.",
  },
  {
    answer: "tree",
    question: "A tall plant with leaves that grows in parks and forests.",
  },
];
